skillsyouneed.com 2014-02-09

# SkillsYouNeed Privacy and Cookie Policy

We take your privacy very seriously at SkillsYouNeed.

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SkillsYouNeed collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of [**www.skillsyouneed.com**](http://www.skillsyouneed.com/) **. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by SkillsYouNeed.  
**  

### Personal Identification Information

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us.

Such information may be given to us in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, filling out a form or sending us an email, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources that we make available on our site.

Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site-related activities or getting a reply to an enquiry. 

### Non-personal Identification Information

SkillsYouNeed.com uses Google Analytics and collects **non-personal identification information** about users whenever they interact with our site. Non-personal identification information includes demographic information such as the country and city in which the user is located. Technical information is also collected, such as browser type, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to SkillsYouNeed, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider. Pageviews and duration of visit are also recorded.

### Cookies

Our site may use third party "cookies" to enhance user experience. Each user's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.

#### Google Adsense

Advertisements on SkillsYouNeed are served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does **NOT** track personal information, such as name, email address, physical address, etc. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

### How we use collected information

SkillsYouNeed may collect and use users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * **To improve the site.**  
We may use feedback to improve our products and services.
  * **To send periodic emails.**  
We may use the email address to respond to enquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If a user decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they may receive occasional emails that may include news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the user would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How we Protect Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of personal information.

### Sharing your Personal Information

**We do not sell, trade, or rent any user personal identification information to others.**

We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our site that links to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

SkillsYouNeed has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes and to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Users acknowledge and agree that it is their responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please use our **[contact us](http://www.skillsyouneed.com/contact.php)** page to get in touch.

**This document was last updated on 7 June 2013.**
